allinoneprofits.com 2019-12-18

# All In One Profits

Buying and selling   
Is Changing. Protect  
Yourself NOW| [ **Massive Advertising**](http://aioptk.com/18ig)  
1 click join,   
1 click send.   
NO Return Emails| [ **Build your list**](https://www.instantcashpromocodes.com/splashpage.php?aff=jwjulian)  
ORU & Promo codes  
Earn more money  
Advertising your Biz| [ **230K In 16 weeks!**](http://digisoftpayline.com/230k.php?alexpto)  
the FREE Tour!  
Instant Commissions!  
100% Payout!| [ **Immediate Income**](http://joinbyinvitation.com/)  
Without selling but  
Giving Away Gifts  
200 Dollar Payments  
---|---|---|---|---  

## Privacy Policy 

Our Privacy Policy and Data Protection and Processing Security is integral part and subject to our [Terms and Conditions of Use](https://allinoneprofits.com/terms.php "Terms"). 

By using our services, or visiting our website, you agree to the policies and practices of our Privacy Policy, Data Protection and Processing Security (the 'Privacy Policy'),and also you accept that we shall collect, process and use your personal information as described below, so please read them carefully. 

**ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND AGREEMENT**

As clearly stated in our legal Terms and Conditions, your Agreement to our Terms and Conditions, therefore to our Privacy Policy and Data Protection and Processing Security, as integral part of our Terms, equals your signature in writing on a written contract, between you and us, has the same value as a written contract and is valid in any legal circumstances.

Customers/Affiliates ('Clients', 'Users') you cannot register, order and use our services, unless you confirm the acknowledgement and the agreement to our legal Terms, to the Privacy Policy, therefore agreeing equals your signature on a written contract with us for this Privacy Policy and Data Protection and Security.

By visiting, accessing, or using our website, you consent to This Privacy Policy, data collecting processing, protection and security. If any policies or practices of this Privacy Policy is unacceptable to you, please do not visit, access, or use our website and services.

By visiting, accessing, or using our website and services, you confirm that you are at least eighteen (18) years old, have the legal capacity to consent to this Privacy Policy, and to agree to be bound by the policies and practices of this Privacy Policy in their entirety and by our Terms and Conditions in their entirety. 

This Privacy Policy explains what Personal Information we collect and process, why we collect it, and how we treat it, in order to be able to provide our services, and governs the way we collect and process data through our website and service, the way we use, secure, maintain and disclose information collected from our customers, visitors to our website and pages. It also describes the choices available and the rights you have regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

This Privacy Policy and Data Protection applies to www.allinoneprofits.com, website and services owned and operated by AIOPBT Group ('we', 'our', 'us', 'company').   
Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, disclose, and safeguard the aggregate information we receive when you visit our website, or our clients websites using our services, and when you use our services as Client.

In the course of providing services to our Clients, we collect and process information. Any information we collect will be stored securely and kept strictly confidential. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including Customer details, email addresses, and other personal information.  
Any information that we obtain, whether you supply it to us or we collect it directly and automatically, will be held with the utmost care and will only be used in ways consistent with your consent. 

We also use some third-party partners to assist us in providing our services, and where applicable this Privacy Policy describes the ways in which they may collect, use, maintain, and disclose information. Nevertheless, the use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which our Clients have engaged us.

If you have any questions about our privacy and data processing practices, please feel free to contact us by e-mail, at [privacy@allinoneprofits.com](mailto:privacy@allinoneprofits.com)

 **CHILDREN PROTECTION**

We do not provide services to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may visit our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are under 18 years old, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information.

 **AGREEMENT TO PRIVACY POLICY AND PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION**

You acknowledge that the services we provide, and any identifiable personal data we collect and process in order to provide to you our services are based solely on your consent.

When you visit our website, order and use our services as our client the data is manually provided by you based on your consent.

By visiting our website, order and use our services as our client and affiliate you are agreeing that we collect automatically some information that will not identify you as person, aggregated data that helps us provide and improve our service you engaged us for.

With this purpose, you are required always to confirm that you have acknowledged and agree to the Privacy Policy and Data Protection Policy and the entirety of our legal Terms and the fact that you cannot register an account and use our services without agreeing and providing your consent.

Your agreement to our legal Terms (valued as contract between parts) listed on the website, including this Privacy Policy, represents the agreement to the contract between you and our company. 

You are required always to confirm that you have requested any information from us or from our clients, and you have acknowledged the Privacy and Data Processing Policies and our legal Terms and agree to our legal policies when you interact with us or with our customers and affiliates and when you register, order and use our services.

You acknowledge that we do not collect your personal data for any purposes that are not designed to help us provide the services our customers engaged us for and your data collection is based on your consent.

The Privacy Policy of our Clients to whom we provide our Service may be different from ours. 

If our Clients` Privacy Policy is significant differently than ours, please make sure that you agree to our Client Privacy Policy or contact the Client whose website you visited, use or subscribe, as it is the data collector for your personal information. We are not responsible or liable for the Clients Privacy Policies, but we process the data accordingly to our standards and policies.

 **UNDERSTANDING PERSONAL DATA**

As used herein, 'Persona Data' or 'Personal Information' means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ('Data Subject'); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, or an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.

 **EU and EEA Zone**

**General Data Protection Regulation ('GDPR')**

General Data Protection Regulation, is the EU Regulation that sets guidelines for the collection and processing of personal information of natural persons, within the European Union (EU), and automatically applies and governs all EU countries.

**Data Controller**  
Art.4 item 7, of the GDPR: 'controller' means the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data.  
**Data Processor**  
Art.4 item 8 of the GDPR: 'processor' means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller.

 **AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING AND PROFILING**

We do NOT collect, use, rent, loan, trade, share, or sell your personal data for in any circumstances or for any purpose other that stated in this privacy Policy, and most important, we do NOt use or do any actions with the purpose of Automated decision-making and Profiling. However, if required, we may do so in order to fulfill obligations imposed by law, in which case we will inform you of any such processing and provide you with an opportunity to object.

 **PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU** **Personal Data You Manually Provide**

  * When you register, subscribe, order, buy and use our services and products

We will ask you to provide, through manually completing the registration form, the following **identifiable** information in order for us to be able to provide our services:   

your full name 
  * email address
  * your phone number
  * address, city, state, country, zip code
  * account Username and password
  * your acknowledgement and agreement to our legal Terms including the Privacy Policy and Data Protection Policies.

In the event that you refuse or cannot provide the data required and the agreement to our legal Terms, including the Privacy Policy, we will be not able to provide you the services. 

You can always choose not to provide us with information. If you withhold information or provide false information, we may restrict or deny your access to our services.

We may also collect at your consent, when you purchase from us, or when pay your affiliate commission, some of your billing details or payment ID, but we do NOT request, know, collect or store any data of your payment card details when you make the payment for our services.

  * We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our website or by e-mail.

For answers to Customer inquiries, we may need to ask you more details, in order to assist you and solve your request for support. You may choose always to provide or not more personal information, we will still do our best to assist you.  

  * When you subscribe to websites or landing pages of our clients, if they use any automated email marketing service and autoresponder, the data collected, by our clients might be transferred to be processed by the email marketing service used by our clients. Because our clients may use various providers, you must refer to their Privacy Policy.

**Data collected when you USE our websites and services**

When you use our website and services we automatically collect certain data stored in our traffic and access reports. Our website automatically records these basic details:

  * your sign up IP address;
  * your login IP address;
  * the last date you accessed our services;
  * the changes you make to your personal profile; 
  * changes made to settings of your account;
  * the referrer URL 
  * service and products access and usage by date and IP

We collect and aggregate these details in our legitimate interest in order to provide you the service, to prevent any unauthorized access, to monitor the server status and the service delivery, as well as for any eventuality of legal purposes and illegal activity prevention. **HOW WE COLLECT THE INFORMATION**

We collect and process the data:

 **Manually, identifiable:** information provided directly by you, manually, through the forms. For example: registration forms as our potential client, registration forms as customer ordering/buying our services and products, support request forms, information required to comply with the KYC regulations and other legal requirements.  

  * **Registration, Customer Records.** Customers provide us with information outlined above in the collection data list, personally identifiable or confidential information. This information may be aggregated to create an administrative record that includes information related to the products and services provided to you, how you use those services, problems related to the services, and notations from our staff about our relationship with you, among other things.

  * **Billing.** We collect information related to the transaction as part of the process of business, as outlined in the above paragraphs about what data we collect from you.  
We do NOT collect, do not have access nor store your card details. We advise you to always check the Privacy Policy of any payment processing option you use online for any purchase.

  * **Customer and Visitor Inquiries.** If you contact us about a problem or with a question we may ask you for specific information related to the reason you have contacted us (Customer Inquiry Information). This information may be tied or input into your Registration and Billing Information. As visitor we may require to identify yourself before answering your inquiries.

**Automatically, non identifiable:** information we obtain automatically when you use our services. For example: we process minimal information about the history of interactions with our website and services access, overall order history, IP history, servers status and performance, etc., the aggregated data history helping us to provide our services without interruption to our customers, to understand what services are most accessed, the services functionality and requirements from our clients.  

  * **Log Files Data**  
We gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. The information we gather is for site administration purpose, to gather information about the visitor or the user and track user movements around the site and analyze statistical factors that help us improve the service. No information is shared unless required for legal purposes.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to track users’ movements around the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information.

  * **COOKIES**  
The cookies we use are only session cookies. This category of cookies does not require consent. With session cookies we keep track when a person is logged in. Once a user is logged in, session cookies allow us to personalize information on our Web site for the user, as well as keep track of pages, content and section to which they have access privileges. Cookies help us determine which particular page and content visitors view, which page and content visitors link to, and which of our services Clients and visitors use. We also use the data collected to keep track and inform our clients about the number of people who have seen and clicked on their links.  
You can restrict the use of cookies or delete them from your browser at any time by configuring your browser settings. However, restricting cookies can interfere with some of the functionality of our website.  
We do NOT store cookies on your browser or any device. Because we use only short time lifespan cookies, session cookies (user input) which are erased when the user closes the browser, just to identify you as user. For the domain to which it belongs we use only first-party cookies which are set by the web server of the visited page and share the same domain.

**If you are a visitor or user from the EU and EEA zone**

**We use cookies that do not require consent:**

  * Accordingly to EU legislation the visitors and users from the EU must be informed and consent obtained for certain categories of cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data that a website asks your browser to store on your computer. The cookie allows the website to "remember" your actions or preferences over time.

  * The Consent is not required if the cookie is used for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication, and strictly necessary in order for the provider of an information society service explicitly required by the user to provide that service.

  * We use cookies that are clearly exempt from consent accordingly to the EU advisory body on data protection- WP2 legislation about cookies,  
\- user-input cookies (session-id) such as firstparty cookies to keep track of the user's input when filling online forms, shopping carts, etc., for the duration of a session or persistent cookies limited to a few hours in some cases  
\- authentication cookies, to identify the user once he has logged in, for the duration of a session  
\- user-centric security cookies, used to detect authentication abuses, for a limited persistent duration

  * You can read more about cookies: <http://ec.europa.eu/ipg/basics/legal/cookies/index_en.htm>

**HOW WE USE THE DATA COLLECTED AND PROCESSED**

**Not personally identifiable and automatically collected:** IP, Browser Information Collected on the Website, Cookies. Statistical Information.

We do not use this data to identify Users individually. We analyze our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials on our website. However, our website logs are automatically collected and not personal identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with individuals who actually browse the site. We use the information provided by the session cookies to keep you logged in to certain areas of the website. We do not use this data to identify Users individually. However, statistical information is shared with, and used by our server provider and payment provider partners in order for us to provide you the service and identify eventual issues.

We use statistical information to operate our software, diagnose problems and administer our website. We may use aggregate information to modify the products and services we offer based on who is visiting our website, and what they are purchasing.

**Personally identifiable, manually collected:**

**Registration and Billing Information.** We use Registration and Billing Information to identify Users individually. Registration and Billing Information is used throughout our business to provide services to you. 

**Customer Inquiries.** We use Customer Inquiry Information to identify Users individually. It is used throughout our business to provide services to you.

Customer Inquiry Information is shared with third parties in the following circumstances:

  * with our server provider to identify and fix problems with services when we are not capable of doing so ourselves. 
  * with the card processing company that is processing the transactions for us

The third parties are providing services based on contracts we have with them. When Customer Inquiry Information is shared with these third parties in this way, the third parties are required to keep this information confidential based on the contract provisions.

**Email lists.** We maintain several email lists to keep customers informed about the service status, service news and addition, and any events that may occur and we need to contact you. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on those lists to anyone. We use the emails to communicate with you to provide you the service.

These emails are NOT Newsletters but service updates and service notification emails and you cannot opt out from the communication with us, unless you request that your account to be removed from our system and data erased, therefore the service will be not provided further.

**Phone number:** The phone number you provide willingly to us, is used by us to contact you in order to provide you the service and to assist you in using our service, registration or billing process. We do not share, sell, rent, lease or trade your phone number to anyone.

**Other disclosures.** We are required to comply with relevant laws, regulations and judicial orders. Information covered by this Privacy Policy, as well as other categories of information, may be disclosed to third parties if we determine, in our sole discretion, that such a disclosure is necessary or required. Within the bounds of the law, we may also disclose this information if in our sole discretion such a disclosure is necessary or required to protect our interests or the interests of our customers, and we may also disclose this information in connection with the sale of our business.

 **CUSTOMERS DATA**

We collect and use personal information from Customers who register and use our Service All the information of our Clients is held in strict confidence.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy policy. We do not sell or share your information with anyone else. We only collect the information as described in this Privacy Policy, so we can provide the services described on our website.

We use the Customers' registration information to authenticate users and provide access to the Service. We also use the email addresses used in the registration information to communicate with our Customers. From time to time, we may contact you via email to notify you of changes to our Service, scheduled maintenance, and information about our service and new products we add.

The Customer is required to update the data provided in the registration form as soon as any change in these data has occurred. 

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you the Service. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Providing your personal data in connection with your use of our service is voluntary, based on your consent.  
Note, however, that the refusal to provide certain data may make it impossible for you to use all or part of the Service functionalities.  
The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service to our customers. 

We use your information to:

  * connect with you;
  * setup your account;
  * operate our service activities; 
  * resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues;
  * provide you the proper access to the website and services;
  * optimize and enhance our services for all customers or for you specifically;
  * monitor the usage of our services, and conduct automated and manual security checks of our services;
  * contact you about changes to our website; 
  * update you about new services or products added; 
  * conduct anti-fraud and identity verification and authentication checks (you authorize us to share your Personal Information with our third-party service providers, who may also conduct their own searches of Information about you);
  * create aggregated and anonymized reporting data about our services.

We will never disclose personally identifiable information about its customers to any third party without customer permission or unless necessary for legal reasons.  
We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you to law enforcement or other government officials for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability. 

**Newsletters and Service Related Emails**

We will not send you Newsletters. When you register your account and place your order, as our Customer you must provide us your email address. 

We will send you administrative information, updates, communicating with you, answering your inquiries, system status, everything that is necessary to provide you the proper Service. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You do not have an option to opt out of these emails, which are not promotional in nature.

You cannot opt-out from receiving the emails from us, the communication being essential for the service we provide to you. If you no longer wish to receive the communication from us, you must request the cancelation of the service. 

If at some point, we will decide to send you informative Newsletters, for purposes not related directly to our services, we shall provide you always a link to unsubscribe from receiving those emails.

You can request anytime that your data and any details about you to be removed from our system, at your sole discretion. **AFFILIATES DATA**

The access to our affiliate program is granted only to our customers who choose to enter into the Affiliate Agreement with us. We do not provide the affiliate option to those who are not our customers. Any information you provide are held in strict confidence. We collect the information so we can generate your commission and meet the tax requirements. We also can use the information collected in the event you breach the Affiliate Agreement and Conduct, and the entire [Terms and Conditions](https://allinoneprofits.com/terms.php "terms") of use as our Customer/Affiliate as required by the law and other legal enforcements. We do not sell or share your information with anyone else.

 **SUBSCRIBERS DATA**

If you are a Subscriber to an email list of our Clients, please refer to the email marketing and autoresponder service Privacy Policy used by our Clients for their websites. If you are a subscriber of one of our Customers` websites, please refer to the customer website privacy Policy, and if you would no longer like to be contacted by our Customer by any means, please contact our Customer that you interact with directly.

 **Customers outsourcing Subscribers` personal data processing**

Subscribers data processing may be outsourced by our Customer(the controller) in regards to the email address and other Subscriber-related information, to the email marketing service provider we use to provide our services to our customers. Please refer to the Privacy Policy and Data protection of the email marketing provider we use.

 **THIRD PARTY PARTNERS**

**Service Providers**

We use other third parties service providers, such payment processing companies, to bill you for services, the servers provider company that hosts our websites, the email marketing provider that maintains your subscribers lists, so we can provide you the Service. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third parties to provide their service. When you interact with our third parties service providers we recommend to read their privacy Policy as well.

We collect information related to the transaction as part of the process of business, including your IP, billing address, and other information related to the transaction. We do not store on our server any of your card details. The third party that is processing the direct card payments is not storing either your card details. We do not know or have access to your card details, this information is shared directly by you with the card processing company during the payment process. We recommend to read their Privacy Policy. 

**Third Party Products**

Normally we sell our own products, but from time to time, we may offer products that are provided by third parties, which are purchased by us with full rights, therefore no data is shared with any third party product provider.

**Sharing Information Regarding the Customers and Subscribers**

We will not share, sell, rent or trade the Customers personal information other than as disclosed within this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to disclose the Customer’s and Subscriber’s personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, Court order, or legal process.  
In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.  
These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes.

If AIOPBT Group will be involved in a merge, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

 **EU and EEA ZONE CUSTOMERS RIGHTS**

There are eight essential rights stated in the EU GDPR for Data protection of the people in the EU and EEA area but we commit ourselves to respect and apply these rights to any customer no matter if you are in or out of the EU and EEA area.

  * **Right to be Informed** \- Art.13 and 14 GDPR - Allows you to know, quite at the moment when your data is collected, how your personal data will be collected, processed, used, shared or transferred, who has access to your data, what rights you have in regards to the data processed, etc.

  * **Right to Access your Data** \- Art. 15 GDPR - Allows you to obtain from us, the confirmation that we process or not personal data that refers to you, and if yes, allows your access to the data and other useful information in regards to your personal data.

  * **Right to Erasure ('right to be forgotten')** \- Art. 17 GDPR - Allows you to request and to obtain from us, the deletion of your personal data, without unjustified delays. However, there are exceptions to this rule, when certain data is processed, retained stored securely on a separate file location than the initial one, with statistical archive purposes and they are processed for fulfilling a legal obligation. 

  * **Right to Rectification** \- Art. 16 GDPR - The data subject shall have the right to obtain from the controller without undue delay the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning him or her. 2Taking into account the purposes of the processing, the data subject shall have the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement.

  * **Right to Restriction of processing** \- Art.18 GDPR - It is a temporary right. The data subject shall have the right to obtain from the controller restriction of processing. Either your data may be inaccurate and the controller needs to verify it or the controller no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but they are required by the data subject for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. Following such request, we will 'freeze' the data, stopping the processing for a while.

  * **Right to data portability** \- Art. 20 GDPR. - The data subject shall have the right to receive the personal data concerning him or her, which he or she has provided to a controller, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from the controller to which the personal data have been provided.

  * **Right to Objec** t - Art. 21 GDPR. - The data subject shall have the right to object, on grounds relating to his or her particular situation, at any time to processing of personal data concerning him or her which is based on point (e) or (f) of Article 6(1), including profiling based on those provisions.

  * **Right to Object to automated individual decision-making, including profiling** The data subject shall have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning him or her or similarly significantly affects him or her. This right does NOT apply if the decision is based on data subject CONSENT.   
**AIOP-Response does NOT make such profiling** that would be followed by automated decision-making with identification of the Customer or subscriber, or any legal effect or to affect the data subject.

**Time Frame:** we shall do our best to answer your requests in maximum 30 days, (but usually much sooner after your request). We can extend this deadline for specific reasons, based on the complexity of your request. In any case, if this time frame is extended, we shall inform you about the extension of the period and the reasons which lead to this.

**Restriction of the access:** in certain situations, we might be not able to offer you the access to entire personal data or to some of them, due to legal restrictions. If we will be in such situation, we shall inform you about the reason of denial.

**No Identification:** in some cases we might be not able to search for your personal data due to the identification details you provide us with your reaquest. In such situations, in case we cannot identify you as being the rightful owner of the personal data, we cannot fulfill your request of exercising your legal rights in regards to your personal data, unless you provide us additional information that would allow us to identify you.

**Exercising your legal rights:** In order to exercise your legal rights outlines above, you can contact us in writing emailing us at [privacy@allinoneprofits.com](mailto:privacy@allinoneprofits.com) or through our Support, and you will receive the answer to all your inquiries and request.

 **INFORMATION SECURITY**

Keeping personal information secure is one of our most significant responsibilities. We safeguard personal information, according to the established security standards and procedures. 

The information set out in this Privacy Policy is protected using industry-standard security measures. However no means of communication or information transmission or storage is totally secure. We cannot be responsible for loss, corruption, or unauthorized acquisition and use of information, or for any damages resulting therefrom, including unauthorized acquisition and use. We do not know who you share your data with, the terminal you are using to write us and transmit your data may be monitored by a third party we do not know and we are not responsible or liable in any way for data transmission over the internet.

**SSL and security**

The security of personal information is important to us. We encrypt the transmission of sensitive information using SSL (secure socket layer technology ).These are generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted, encrypted during transmission and receiving data on internet. However there is not yet known a 100% secure method for encrypted transmission over the Internet.

**Payments security**

Transactions between you and our website may involve third party online payment services and direct card payment. Our payment page is SSL encrypted. We collect information related to the transaction as part of the process of business, including your IP, billing address, and other information related to the transaction. The effective payment is processed through the card gateway processor that is a PCI level 1 compliant, the highest level, and transactions with cards enrolled in 3DSecure are by default processed through the 3DSecure page of your bank. We do not store on our server any of your card details. The third party that is processing the direct card payments is not storing either your card details.

**Your log in details security**

Your account is protected by username and password. We do not share your log in credential with anyone. We recommend that you never give your log in details to anyone. Keep your email address safe, because the log in credentials may be retrieved by anyone who has access to your email address. Do not give your password to anyone. If you enter a section of our website that requires a password, you should log out when you leave. You should always log out when you access the members area of any website that requires log in, as a precaution.

**Your personal profile security**

If you want to make changes to your personal information, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by cancelling your payment and by contacting Support. We will respond to your request to access within 24-72 hours. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Non-Disclosure of Personal Information**

Our customer support staff members are prohibited through the staff contract provisions, either during or after their service with us, from disclosing Personal Information to any person or entity outside of our company, including family members. Our customer support staff members do not have access to sensitive areas or sensitive data of yours, but just minimal data such as name, email address or phone number, identifiable only and if, you provide such data through Customer Inquiries. Only the management team and technical staff has access to your entire data collected or processed by us and disclosing your personal information only as stated and enforced in this privacy Policy.

**Facebook Connect or other OpenID**

For security reasons, our website doesn`t use Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider.

**Customer Testimonials/Reviews**

Our customers have the option to post customer testimonials/reviews on the Website which may contain personal information. These are unsolicited reviews, we just made available the technical part for submission in customer`s account, in case a customer wants to submit a review. These reviews may contain personal information you share at your own will, that are displaying publicly on our website. We are not requesting or collecting such possible data disclosed by you and is does not imply our liability for publicly share.  
If you wish to update or delete your testimonial/review you can do so, within your account.

You may also post reviews on various social media or forums or other website, including Video reviews, which may contain data that are publicly shared by you. We are not responsible or liable for your personal data sharing. 

**Press release, online magazine publishing platform**

We provide a publishing platform to our Clients. We are not responsible or liable for any personal information you share publicly on your articles that might be seen, access, copied or shared by any visitor to the website.

 **LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Our Clients may include and send, in their communication with you, links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by our website.

 **SOCIAL MEDIA WIDGETS**

Our website doesn`t use Social Media Widgets and any other third party advertising App.

 **DIRECT MARKETING**

We do not send you direct marketing materials promoting services, products, facilities, or offers from third parties sources using information collected from you.  
Subject to applicable laws and regulations, in the event that we decide to send to you such marketing materials from time to time, you will always have the opportunity to opt-in to such communications and will only send them to you if you consent.  
We will not provide your Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing or other unrelated purposes without your written consent.

 **ACCURACY AND RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We take reasonable and practicable steps to ensure that your personal information held by us is accurate with regard to the purposes for which it is to be used, and is not kept longer than is necessary for the fulfillment of the purpose for which it is to be used, which is when your business relationship with us ends, unless the further retention of your personal information is otherwise permitted or required by applicable laws and regulations

 **UNSOLICITED SUBMISSIONS**

We cannot agree to obligations of confidentiality or nondisclosure with regard to any unsolicited information you submit to us, regardless of the method or medium chosen. By submitting unsolicited information or materials to us, you or anyone acting on your behalf, agree and understand that any such information or materials will not be considered confidential or proprietary. We do not provide any facility for sending or receiving private or confidential electronic communications.

 **EU and EEA 'DATA SUBJECTS'  
PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR DATA TRANSFER OUTSIDE THE EEA**

The data is collected, processed and stored within the EU. Our servers, trading offices and the third parties we share your data with, in order to provide you the service, are located in the EU.

If we will provide any personal data to third party service supplier entities outside the EEA, in order to provide, enhance, or expand our services, we shall take the appropriate measures that the third party entity we work with is protecting your personal data accordingly to this Privacy Policy and Data Protection. 

  * for service suppliers within the USA, standard agreement approved by EU or their prove that they are enrolled in the USA Privacy Shield program.

  * for other service suppliers outside the EEA standard agreement approved by EU.

By accepting this Privacy and Data Protection and Security Policy, you agree to collecting, processing, storing or transfer. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. **COOPERATION WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT, LEGAL DOCUMENTS, MONITORING SERVICES**

Customers are solely responsible for ensuring that materials disseminated or posted using our services comply with this Privacy Policy, relevant laws, provisions of our legal Terms and Condition of use, to which the Customers agreed to. We do not review, edit, censor, or take responsibility for any information customers or users may create. Because of this, we cannot accept any responsibility from customers, users, or third parties, which results from inaccurate, unsuitable, offensive, or illegal content or transactions.

We do take the appropriate measures if we find out that any of our Customers/Affiliates breaches our legal Terms and Conditions they agreed to and if affects us and you, in any way we shall always inform you about the measures we take.

We will take the appropriate measures against any visitor or subscriber to our website, performs inappropriate actions that are against our legal Terms, local and international regulations, which may affect the company, the brand and our customers data protection and security.

We are required to and will disclose information, including information that Users may consider confidential, upon receipt of a proper law enforcement request or to otherwise comply with relevant law. We assume no obligation to inform a customer or User that information has been provided and in some cases may be prohibited by law from giving such notice. We may also disclose such information when it is necessary for us to protect ourselves, or others, from harm.

 **VIEW, CHANGE OR REMOVE INFORMATION.**

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may change or delete your profile information at any time by going to your profile page from the menu, then the information will be updated. Please contact us if you need assistance in updating or reviewing your information. To modify or update your Payment Information please contact us, as for security protection of your account, you cannot do this from within your account.

 **DELETION OF PROCESSED DATA**

After inactivation of the Customer's account from the Service, we shall store information related to the Customer and the Subscriber, as well as any statistical data concerning the User Account for 45 days (in the case of a payable account). The processing of personal data after the inactivation may only involve holding of the same data, unless performance of other operations on the data has been imposed on us by applicable regulations or competent authorities.   
Free accounts data is stored for a period of 30 days .

We will store personal data, in accordance with the above provision, solely for the purposes of possible activation (reactivation) of the account, accordingly to our [Terms of Service](https://allinoneprofits.com/terms.php "terms") or complying to our duties as specified in the applicable regulations or as imposed by the competent authorities. 

After the periods mentioned above, the account will be deleted from the Service and the recovery will not be possible.  
After the Client Account is erased from our service, the personal data of the client is stored on a separate location on our backup server. The client may exercise the rights of requesting data removal unless performance of other operations on the data has been imposed on us by applicable regulations or competent authorities.

 **INFORMATION MISUSE AND SPAM**

You may obtain personal information from and about another of our clients or visitors, if this is the case, you are not allowed to disclose this information to anyone else without the consent of that person. We hate Spam more than you may think. And we do mean that Privacy Protection must protect the personal data.   
Any information you may obtain through our website and service about us or other site users or subscribers, cannot be used by you or others to send unsolicited commercial e-mail or to send unsolicited communications via our website service or other communication systems.

 **MODIFICATION OF PRIVACY POLICY**

We may update our privacy policy at any time, to reflect changes to our information practices. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have, collect and process about you and your account as our customer.

If we make any material changes, in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection and processing, we will notify you or our client, by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

However, if users have opted out of all communication with us, our website, or deleted their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in the new manner.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy and Data Protection, you may contact us by email at [privacy@allinoneprofits.com](mailto:privacy@allinoneprofits.com), by Phone at +17029972417 or contact our Support.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 2018-05-23.
